Guide to the Stanford Channel Master Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Channel master videorecordings
1995-2001
V0232
Stanford Channel (Television station: Stanford, Calif.)
198 Linear feet
Master videotapes from programs produced and aired by the Stanford Channel.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Access: consult the University Archivist for access.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Stanford Channel, the university's educational cable television channel, debuted in 1995 as Channel 51; it ceased operations in October 2001. When it began in 1995, it was one of the few cable broadcast outlets in the nation owned and operated by a private university. Its programs included university events, lectures, arts programming and sports.
Description of the Collection
Master videotapes from programs produced and aired by the Stanford Channel.
Access Terms
Stanford Channel (Television station: Stanford, Calif.); Educational television programs.; Television broadcasting--California.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Videos (Box 1)
  - Stanford Sports
    - Women's Volleyball vs UCLA, 98-015 (Box 1)
    - Women's Volleyball vs Oregon State, 98-017 (Box 1)
    - Women's Volleyball vs. Oregon State, 99-026 (Box 2)
  - TSC Special Presentation
    - Graduate Student Tax Advice Seminar, 98-010 (Box 1)
    - Learn & Live, 98-011 (Box 1)
    - Stanford Baseball LIVE vs. USC, 98-012 (Box 1)
    - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve: An Island of Discovery, 98-013 (Box 1)
    - Overseas Studies Program at Forty, 98-014 (Box 1)
    - 1968 Across the Generations, 98-016 (Box 1)
    - Meeting the Year 2000 Computer Challenge: Schools, Colleges & the Millenium Bug, 98-018/a (Box 1)
    - Meeting the Year 2000 Computer Challenge: Schools, Colleges & the Millenium Bug, 98-018/b (Box 1)
    - Beyond Words: New Tools for the Learning Community, 99-019 (Box 1)
    - Stanford Baseball LIVE vs. Washington State, 99-020 (Box 1)
    - Race, Ethnicity and Gender: An Interdisciplinary Collaboration Part 1: Policy in Action: The Location Impact of National Welfare Reform in San Mateo County, 00-028/a (Box 2)
    - Race, Ethnicity and Gender: An Interdisciplinary Collaboration Part 2: Race, Povery and Privilege: A Latino Perspective, 00-028/b (Box 2)
    - Cancer Support Group: A Positive Solution, 01-029 (Box 2)
    - Stanford Baseball LIVE vs. USC, 99-021 (Box 2)
    - Stanford Baseball LIVE vs. Cal Poly SLO, 99-022 (Box 2)
    - Pacific Vision: Stanford's Asia/Pacific Scholars Program, 99-023 (Box 2)
    - Becoming Stanford: The Making of an American University Part 1: The Founding, 99-024/a (Box 2)
    - Becoming Stanford: The Making of an American University Part 2: The Transformation, 99-024/b (Box 2)
    - Men's Tennis vs. UCLA -- LIVE ON TSC, 99-025 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Presents
    - Tools for Executive Survival, 95-101 (Box 3)
    - Computers, Privacy and the Law, 95-102 (Box 3)
    - The Athlete's Forum, 95-103 (Box 3)
    - Stockdale Triumphs, 95-104 (Box 3)
    - Asia: The View from Within, 95-105 (Box 3)
    - The Human Genome Project, Part 1: Putting the Human Genome Project in Perspective, 95-106 (Box 3)
    - The Human Genome Project Part 2: David Botstein, 95-107 (Box 3)
    - How Sequencing Genes Will Affect Our Day-to Day Lives, 95-108 (Box 3)
    - The Human Genome Project, Part 4: Latest Developments, 95-109 (Box 3)
    - A Fragile Fortress: Louis Pasteur's Legacy of Hope., 95-110 (Box 3)
    - The 105th Convocation of Stanford University, 95-111 (Box 3)
    - Political Change from the 1960s to the 1990s, 95-112 (Box 3)
    - Genetic Testing: Expectations, Implications and Options, 95-113 (Box 4)
    - Can We Talk: Free Speech, Speech Codes and the First Amendment, 95-114 (Box 4)
    - Earthquakes in the Holy Land, 95-115 (Box 4)
    - Children Now, Part 1: Children, News Media and Violence, 96-116 (Box 4)
    - Children Now, Part 2: TV Violence: The Kid's Point of View, 96-117 (Box 4)
    - Children Now, Part 3: Where Kids Get their News, 96-118 (Box 4)
    - E Pluribus Unum, American National Identity/Identities, Part 1, 96-119 (Box 4)
    - E Pluribus Unum, American National Identity/Identities, Part 2, 96-120 (Box 4)
    - E Pluribus Unum? American National Identity/Identities, Part 3, 96-121 (Box 4)
    - E Pluribus Unum? American National Identity/Identities, Part 4, 96-122 (Box 4)
    - Dedication of the William Gates Computer Science Building, 96-123 (Box 4)
    - Commission on Technology in Teaching and Learning: A Midterm Update, 96-124 (Box 5)
    - Law and Affirmative Action, 96-125 (Box 5)
    - In Praise of Politics, 96-126 (Box 5)
    - Global Environmental Diplomacy -- A Speech by Warren Christopher, 96-127 (Box 5)
    - GSB Women: Working Toward Solutions, 96-128 (Box 5)
    - GSB Women: Getting to the Top, 96-129 (Box 5)
    - Inclusive Narratives of American History, 96-130 (Box 5)
    - 1996 Commencement tape #1, 96-131 (Box 5)
    - 1996 Commencement tape #2, 96-131 (Box 5)
    - The 106th Opening Convocation, 96-133 (Box 5)
    - Hopkins Marine Station: The Blue Revolution, 96-134 (Box 5)
    - The State of the University, 1996, 96-135 (Box 5)
    - Security and Freedom Through Encryption, Part 1, 96-136 (Box 5)
    - Security and Freedom Through Encryption, Parts 2 and 3, 96-137/a (Box 6)
    - Security and Freedom Through Encryption, Parts 2 and 3, 96-137/b (Box 6)
    - Security and Freedom Through Encryption, Part 4, 96-138 (Box 6)
    - Grapes in the '90s: Serving Grapes at Stanford, 96-139 (Box 6)
    - Saving Our Cities, 96-140 (Box 6)
    - An Insider's View of Washington, 96-141 (Box 6)
    - Free Speech, Free Education, and the Protection of Children: Values in Conflict, 96-142 (Box 6)
    - Pursuing Your Passion: Career Goals in the Late 1990s, 96-143 (Box 6)
    - Common Ground: Business and the Environment, 96-144 (Box 6)
    - Off the Beaten Path: Innovation in Recurring Mass Tort Litigation, 96-145 (Box 6)
    - The Future of Nuclear Deterrence, 96-146 (Box 6)
    - An Address by the Prime Minister of Malaysia, 97-147 (Box 6)
    - Interview with Gareth Evans, 97-148 (Box 7)
    - Memories of a Champion: Greg Lemond, 97-149 (Box 7)
    - Cloning Sheep; Cloning People?, 97-150 (Box 7)
    - "Dreams of a City: Creating East Palo Alto", 97-151 (Box 7)
    - Hong Kong in Transition: Contexts and Implications, 97-152 (Box 7)
    - Risk Management and Mitigation for Natural Hazards, 97-154 (Box 7)
    - If You Want to Build Character, Try Something Else: Ethics and Sports in 1997 and Beyond, 97-155/a (Box 7)
    - If You Want to Build Character, Try Something Else: Ethics and Sports in 1997 and Beyond, 97-155/b (Box 7)
    - If You Want to Build Character, Try Something Else: Ethics and Sports in 1997 and Beyond, 97-155/c (Box 7)
    - The Spirit of Mission San Jose, 97-156 (Box 7)
    - The Petroleum Industry and Global Warming, 97-157 (Box 7)
    - 1997 Commencement Ceremonies at Stanford, 97-158 (Box 8)
    - The Present and Future of American Journalism, 97-159 (Box 8)
    - New Challenges to U.S. Policy in the Balkans tape #1, 97-160 (Box 8)
    - New Challenges to U.S. Policy in the Balkans tape #2, 97-160 (Box 8)
    - Stanford and Yamaha Present "Sondius", 97-161 (Box 8)
    - 1997 Opening Convocation, 97-162 (Box 8)
    - Connections: The History of OTL, 97-163 (Box 8)
    - The Long Boom: Causes and Effects of Economic Policy from 1982 - 1997 and Beyond, Part 1, 97-164/a (Box 8)
    - The Long Boom: Causes and Effects of Economic Policy from 1982 - 1997 and Beyond, Part 2, 97-164/b (Box 8)
    - ME210: An Experience in Product-Based Learning, 97-165 (Box 8)
    - Yahoo! Jerry and Dave's Excellent Venture, 97-166 (Box 8)
    - The End of the Beginning: The Emergence of a New Russia, 97-167 (Box 8)
    - Lizzie Borden on Trial: A Dramatization, 97-168 (Box 8)
    - Ties That Bind: Redefining American Families, 97-169 (Box 9)
    - Innovation and Change: The Direction of Financial Services, 97-170 (Box 9)
    - Challenges in Entrepreneurship, 97-171 (Box 9)
    - Strategy and Organization in the Internet Age, 97-172 (Box 9)
    - Changing Rivals, Changing Partners: Issues in International Diplomacy, 97-173 (Box 9)
    - Does the Constitution Still Work? Perspectives on the Framers' Vision, 97-174 (Box 9)
    - The State of the University, 1997, 97-175 (Box 9)
    - Conversations with a Champion: The Spectacular Career of Eddy Merckx, 97-176 (Box 9)
    - White House Conference on Climate Change: Challenge of Global Warming, 97-177 (Box 9)
    - Ending Civil Wars: The Challenges of Mediating and Implementing Peace Accords, 97-178 (Box 9)
    - Race in America: What is the Agenda?, 97-179 (Box 9)
    - The New Mexico City, 97-180 (Box 11)
    - A Soft, Crash Landing: How the Republic of Korea, China and the West Can Advance Korean Unification. Part 1: The Political Prerequisites for Korean Unification, 97-181/a (Box 11)
    - A Soft, Crash Landing: How the Republic of Korea, China, and the West Can Advance Korean Unification. Part 2: The Economic Prerequisites for Korean Unification tape #1, 97-181/b (Box 11)
    - A Soft, Crash Landing: How the Republic of Korea, China, and the West Can Advance Korean Unification. Part 2: The Economic Prerequisites for Korean Unification, 97-181/b (Box 11)
    - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution, 98-101/a (Box 11)
    - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution, 98-101/b (Box 11)
    - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution, 98-101/c (Box 11)
    - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution, 98-101/d (Box 11)
    - Dream the Boldest Dream, 98-182 (Box 11)
    - California Summit on Race in America tape #1, 98-183/a (Box 11)
    - California Summit on Race in America, 98-183/a (Box 11)
    - California Summit on Race in America tape #1, 98-183/b (Box 11)
    - California Summit on Race in America, 98-183/b (Box 11)
    - California Summit on Race in America tape #1, 98-183/c (Box 11)
    - California Summit on Race in America, 98-183/c (Box 11)
    - Software's Future, 98-184 (Box 12)
    - Issues for Schooling in the Next Century, 98-185 (Box 12)
    - 1998 Commencement Ceremonies tape #1, 98-186 (Box 12)
    - 1998 Commencement Ceremonies, 98-186 (Box 12)
    - Economic Reform in Korea An Address by Kim Dae-jung, president of Republic of Korea, 98-187 (Box 12)
    - Opening Convocation, 1998, 98-188 (Box 12)
    - Foreign Policy Decision-Making in the U.S. tape #1, 98-189 (Box 12)
    - Foreign Policy Decision-Making in the U.S., 98-189 (Box 12)
    - Forum on Global Change tape #1, 98-190 (Box 12)
    - Forum on Global Change, 98-190 (Box 12)
    - Technology and You: Building Bridges or Building Walls?, 98-191 (Box 12)
    - Who's Watching Out for Our Kids?, 98-192 (Box 12)
    - How DO Judges Decide? Precedent versus Philosophy, and the Role of Law Clerks, 98-193 (Box 12)
    - A Tribute to Archibald Cox and Panel: The Future of the Independent Counsel:, 98-194 (Box 12)
    - A Discussion of Impeachment, 98-195 (Box 13)
    - GSB Women: Leading the Way, 98-196/a (Box 13)
    - GSB Women: Leading the Way, 98-196/b (Box 13)
    - GSB Women: Leading the Way, 98-196/c (Box 13)
    - GSB Women: Leading the Way, 98-196/d (Box 13)
    - GSB Women: Leading the Way, 98-196/e (Box 13)
    - 1998 State of the University Address, 98-197 (Box 13)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons tape #1, 98-198/a (Box 13)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons, 98-198/a (Box 13)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons, 98-198/b (Box 13)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons, 98-198/c (Box 13)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons, 98-198/d (Box 13)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons tape #1, 98-198/e (Box 14)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons tape #2, 98-198/e (Box 14)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons tape #1, 98-198/f (Box 14)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons tape #2, 98-198/f (Box 14)
    - National Security Forum on Biological and Chemical Weapons, 98-198/g (Box 14)
    - Culture, Ecology, and Conservation in Amazonia, 98-199/a (Box 14)
    - Culture, Ecology, and Conservation in Amazonia, 98-199/b (Box 14)
    - Culture, Ecology, and Conservation in Amazonia, 98-199/c (Box 14)
    - To the Mountain Top...The Journey Continues, 99-102 (Box 14)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society, 99-103/a (Box 14)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society tape #1, 99-103/b (Box 14)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society tape #2, 99-103/b (Box 14)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society, 99-103/c (Box 14)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society, 99-103/d (Box 14)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society, 99-103/e (Box 15)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society tape #1, 99-103/f (Box 15)
    - Models for Diversity: The University's Role in Shaping An Inclusive Society tape #2, 99-103/f (Box 15)
    - Shaking the Foundations: The West Coact Conference on Progressive Lawyering, 99-104/a (Box 15)
    - Shaking the Foundations: The West Coast Conference on Progressive Lawyering, 99-104/b (Box 15)
    - Shaking the Foundations: The West Coast Conference on Progressive Lawyering, 99-104/c (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues tape #1, 99-105/a (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues tape #2, 99-105/a (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues, 99-105/b (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues tape #1, 99-105/c (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues tape #2, 99-105/c (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues tape #1, 99-105/d (Box 15)
    - Close Encounters: Ethnographic Perspectives on Global Issues tape #2, 99-105/d (Box 15)
    - Law, Science and Technology at Stanford, in Silicon Valley and in the Global Economy, 99-106 (Box 15)
    - Setting the Stage: Elements and Conditions of Black Popular Culture, 99-107/a (Box 15)
    - Setting the Stage: Elements and Conditions of Black Popular Culture, part 2, 99-107/b (Box 16)
    - Limits of Performance: A Presidential Symposium in the Arts and Humanities: Part 1 tape #1, 99-108/a (Box 16)
    - Limits of Performance: A Presidential Symposium in the Arts and Humanities: Part 1 tape #2, 99-108/a (Box 16)
    - Limits of Performance: Part 2 tape #1, 99-108/b (Box 16)
    - Limits of Performance: Part 2 tape #2, 99-108/b (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #1, 99-109/a (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #2, 99-109/b (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #3, 99-109/c (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #4, 99-109/d (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #5, 99-109/e (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #6, 99-109/f (Box 16)
    - Facing the Courts of Law and Public Opinion: Social Science Evidence on Diversity in Higher Education Program #7, 99-109/g (Box 16)
    - The Study of Foreign Languages in the New Century #1 tape #1, 99-110/a (Box 16)
    - The Study of Foreign Languages in the New Century #1 tape #2, 99-110/a (Box 16)
    - The Study of Foreign Languages in the New Century #2, 99-110/b (Box 17)
    - The Study of Foreign Languages in the New Century #3, 99-110/c (Box 17)
    - The Study of Foreign Languages in the New Century #4, 99-110/d (Box 17)
    - 1999 Commencement Ceremonies tape #1, 99-111 (Box 17)
    - 1999 Commencement Ceremonies tape #2, 99-111 (Box 17)
    - Sustainable Development Summit: Confronting Sprawl, 99-112 (Box 17)
    - California and Asia: Partners for the Future, 99-113 (Box 17)
    - 1999 Opening Convocation, 99-114 (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #1, 99-115/a (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #2, 99-115/b (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #3 tape #1, 99-115/c (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #3 tape #2, 99-115/c (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #4 tape #1, 99-115/d (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #4 tape #2, 99-115/d (Box 17)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #5, 99-115/e (Box 18)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #6 tape #1, 99-115/f (Box 18)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #6 tape #2, 99-115/f (Box 18)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #7 tape #1, 99-115/g (Box 18)
    - Making the Spirit of 20th and 21st Century Culture, Program #7 tape #2, 99-115/g (Box 18)
    - Convocation on Business: Wall Street's Romance With Technology: Will the Magic Last?, 99-116 (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #1: "Thoughts on the Relevance on Dogen's Thought", 99-117/a (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #2: "Dogen Zenji's Zazen", 99-117/b (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #3: "Dogen Zenji's Standards for Community Practice", 99-117/c (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #4: "Dogen's 300 Koans and Kana Shobogenzo", 99-117/d (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #5: Panel Discussion, 99-117/e (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #6: "History of the Soto Zen School", 99-117/f (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #7: "Soto Zen in America", 99-117/g (Box 18)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #8: "Dreaming Peace in an Age of War", 99-117/h (Box 19)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #9: "Mountains Hidden in Mountains: Dogen's Nature", 99-117/i (Box 19)
    - Dogen Zen and Its Relevance for Our Time #10: "Panel Discussion and Closing Remarks", 99-117/j (Box 19)
    - Globalization: Brave New World or Plus ca Change?, 99-118 (Box 19)
    - Bing Wing Re-Opening Ceremonies, 99-119 (Box 19)
    - International Consortium of Investigative Journalism: Awards Dinner & Keynote Address tape #1, 99-120 (Box 19)
    - International Consortium of Investigative Journalism: Awards Dinner & Keynote Address tape #2, 99-120 (Box 19)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at the Turn of the Century tape #1, 99-121/a (Box 19)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at the Turn of the Century tape #2, 99-121/a (Box 19)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at Turn of the Century #2, 99-121/b (Box 19)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at Turn of the Century #3, 99-121/c (Box 19)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at Turn of the Century #2, 99-121/d (Box 19)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at Turn of the Century #5, 99-121/e (Box 19)
    - Code and Other Laws of Cyberspace, 00-123/a (Box 20)
    - Cyberspace and Privacy: A New Legal Paradigm, 00-123/b (Box 20)
    - Cyberspace and Privacy: A New Legal Paradigm?, 00-123/c (Box 20)
    - Cyberspace and Privacy: A New Legal Paradigm? #3, 00-123/d (Box 20)
    - Cyberspace and Privacy: A New Legal Paradigm #4, 00-123/e (Box 20)
    - Cyberspace and Privacy: A New Legal Paradigm #5 'Private Communications', 00-123/f (Box 20)
    - Land Use Decisions in Silicon Valley, 00-124 (Box 20)
    - African Americans: Research and Policy Perspectives at Turn of the Century #6, 99-121/f (Box 20)
    - Andrei Sakharov: His Legacy Ten Years Later, 99-122/a (Box 20)
    - Andrei Sakharov: His Legacy Ten Years Later tape #1, 99-122/b (Box 20)
    - Andrei Sakharov: His Legacy Ten Years Later tape #2, 99-122/b (Box 20)
    - Andrei Sakharov: His Legacy Ten Years Later tape #1, 99-122/c (Box 20)
    - Andrei Sakharov: His Legacy Ten Years Later tape #2, 99-122/c (Box 20)
    - The State of the University, 2000, 00-125 (Box 21)
    - Will Spiritual Robots Replace Humanity by 2100? tape #2, 00-126/a (Box 21)
    - Will Spiritual Robots Replace Humanity by 2100?, 00-126/b (Box 21)
    - Will Spiritual Robots Replace Humanity by 2100?, 00-126/c (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/a (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/b (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/c (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/d (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/e (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/f (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/g (Box 21)
    - Will Spiritual Robots Replace Humanity by 2100? tape #1, 00-126/a (Box 21)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/h (Box 22)
    - The Pioneering Efforts of Women in Medicine and the Medical Sciences, 00-127/ii (Box 22)
    - At Home in the World: A Conversation with Joyce Maynard, 00-128 (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration: Program #1: "Welcome" and "Travel the Road from 1969 to the Present", 00-129/a (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #2: Research in a Business School, 00-129/b (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #3: The Evolution of Entrepreneurship: Stanford and Silicon Valley, 00-129/c (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #4: Issues in Small, Rapidly Growing Companies, 00-129/d (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #5: How Should Resources Be Allocated in Markets for Health Care?, 00-129/e (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #6: Strategies and Innovations in Electronic Commerce, 00-129/f (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #7: The Political Economy of Growth and Development, 00-129/g (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #8: Game Theory and Management tape #1, 00-129/h (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #8: Game Theory and Management tape #2, 00-129/h (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #9: Finance at the GSB tape #1, 00-129/i (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #9: Finance at the GSB tape #2, 00-129/i (Box 22)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #10: Measured Optimism: Women and Minorities in the New Economy, 00-129/j (Box 23)
    - Stanford GSB: 75th Anniversary Celebration/Program #11: An Ethic for the New Global Economy, 00-129/k (Box 23)